Guide to the New-York Historical Society Schenectady Collection 1688?-1883, undated (bulk, 1710s-1840s) MS 544
New-York Historical Society
- Petition, undated; 228124 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to Members of the Council of Appointment regarding the appointment of Andrew Cowan as inspector
- Act, undated; 228125 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Act to Fortify town of Schenectady
- Return of Votes, undated; 228126 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Voting returns for Supervisor, Town Clerk, Assessors
- True Estimate, undated; 228128 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  True Estimate by the Assessors of the City of Schenectady
- List, undated; 228129 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  List of Names now in Prince Town Discluded off the Tasel (?) List of the City of Schenectady
- Act, undated; 228130 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Act to enforce part of an Act entitled An Act for Raising 50 pounds in the Township of Schenectady
- List, undated; 228131 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Undated list of residents of Schenectady with a number of pounds after their names
- Notice of Meeting, April 28; 228132 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Notice of an annual meeting for the election of officers for District No. 1, 3rd and 4th Ward of City of Schenectady signed by M. Kendell, Trustee for District
- Schenectady Patent, undated; 228133 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Copy of the boundaries of the Schenectady Patent
- List of Votes, undated; 228134 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  List of votes for Governor (Dewitt Clinton received 26 votes) and For Assembly
- Receipt, undated; 228135 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Receipt between Alexander Stouck and Peter Sanders
- List of Names, undated; 228136 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  List is as follows: Abraham Fonda; Christofer Yates; Isaac Vrooman; Albert Mabie; John Empey; Abraham Switts; Cornelis D. Volgen; Henry van Driesen; Cornelis Van Dyck; John Peck; Cornelis Van Slyck
- Account, undated; 228137 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Account of Henry R. Wendell
- Monthly Bill, undated; 228138 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Monthly bill of District No. 1, 3rd and 4th Ward of City of Schenectady to Henry R. Wendell
- Petition, undated; 228139 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition for new town of Glenville between Legislature of the State of New York and Freeholders and Electors on the North side of the Mohawk River
- Receipt, undated; 228140 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Receipt between H.R. Wendell and M. Trotter
- Receipts - Dutch, undated; 228141 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  receipts between Abraham Wempel/Ephriam Smith and Jacobus Van Slyck/Stin Van Dirk
- Draft Proposal - Dutch, undated; 228142 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Proposal to supply a minister in place of Rev. Thomas Brower for the Dutch Church at Schenectady
- Petition, undated; 228143 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to Judge and Adjutant Justices of the Court Of Common Pleas from John Sanders for a Ferry
- Field Notes, undated; 228144 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  One page of field notes of a Survey along the Mohawk River
- Resolution, undated; 228145 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Resolution by the Citizens of the 3rd/4th Ward of the City of Schenectady that Joseph Shuntleff, Esq. will represent the city in the State Legislature
- Petition, undated; 228146 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to the Honorable James Delaney from the Inhabitants of the Township of Schenectady to fortify the township
- Page of script, undated; 228147 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scrap of paper with handwriting practice of Mary Empie
- Scrap of paper with handwriting practice, undated; 228148 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Note requesting John Empey send Unger Dorkin money
- Letter, undated; 228149 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Letter to John Sanders from Arent Vedder regarding cow hides
- Public Notice, undated; 228150 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to the State Legislature to authorize commissioners to hear and determine if the said common lands should be divided from the Freeholders and Inhabitants of the Township of Schenectady
- Petition, undated; 228151 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Petition to the State Legislature from John Sanders for a toll bridge across the Mohawk River
- Directory of Names, undated; 228152 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Directory of names and professions